huaweidevice.co.in 2015-06-09

# Privacy Policy | Huawei Device

The following information describes how Huawei would collect and use your personal information to provide services that you request or when you choose to provide us with your personal information.

######  Information Collection

Huawei fully respects your privacy, and shall spare no effort to protect your personal information. Generally, you will not be required to provide any personal information for browsing this Website.

In order to measure the effectiveness of our online presence, some pages on this Website may use cookies, which are small text files that a site transfers to a user’s (visitor’s) hard disk or browser for added functionality or for tracking site usage. Huawei may use cookies to log your IP address and to determine the path users take on our site and to identify repeat users of our site, but we do not link your IP address to your personal information. If you do not wish to receive cookies, or want to be notified of when they are placed, you may set your web browser to do so, if your browser permits. 

For specific purposes, in case you provide your name, gender, category and number of credentials, date of birth, country, title, occupation, contact details, services or information desired, customer code and other similar personal information that are required for registration or reading E-information by voluntarily filling in forms, you will be deemed having understood and accepted the use of your personal information and agreed that Huawei uses your personal information for the specific purposes. 

######  Use of Information Collected 

Huawei will not sell or rent your personal information at any time under any circumstance. Your personal information will only be used for Huawei business purposes such as, to meet your requests for certain products, documentation and/or services, to send solicited information, to process an order, to conduct a transaction, to handle a job application or to perform market research. Your personal information may be shared with other Huawei offices or subsidiaries around the world. 

However, Huawei may provide certain portion of your personal information to law executive organs and government authorities as so requested; and Huawei might disclose certain portion of your personal information within a strictly limited scope of recipients when Huawei reasonably thinks it is necessary for protecting Huawei, its customers or the public. You shall have foreseen and agreed to the occurrence of such events when you provide your personal information. 

######  Disclosure of Your Information to Third Parties 

Huawei’s Website contains several links to the Websites or web addresses of third parties, Huawei will not disclose your personal information to those third parties and shall not be responsible for the third parties’ privacy policies. 

Huawei may share your personal information with its business partners to better fulfill your requests for products and/or services. Certainly, Huawei will only share your personal information with its business partners with your consent. If you do not wish to receive marketing materials from any of Huawei’s business partners, please do not provide your contact information via the Internet or you may directly require them to remove your information from their contact list. 

######  Securing Your Information 

Huawei has endeavored to take commercially reasonable measures to prevent unauthorized access to and improper use of your personal information collected by registered or any other means mentioned above via your use of this Website. While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure the security of the information you transmit to us, and so we urge you to take every possible precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often, use a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure browser. 

######  Supporting Children’s Privacy 

Huawei’s Websites do not target, and are not intended to attract children under the age of 13. Huawei does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13 or send them requests for personal information.
